所以接下来的比赛就是，因为我喜欢比赛。
So this next one is,
it's more race because I love the race.
接下来的问题是我多次在
This next problem is one that
I've gotten multiple times at
很多不同的采访
many different interviews.
不用那么平平平平的
It is without using that flat,
这是一个新的方法，直到今年才会存在。
which is a new method,
which didn't exist until this year.
这会为你做的
Which will do this for you.
但是，在不使用 .flat 的情况下，创建将平铺数组的函数。
But without using .flat, create
a function that will flatten an array.
通过平坦化一个数组，它是数组阵列，数组，
And by flattening an array it means,
it's an array of arrays, of arrays,
不管嵌套深度有多深
it doesn't matter how deeply nested it is.
然后我要你把所有的阵列
Then I want you to take
out all the arrays and
只要给我一个数组，将所有值都放入一个数组中。
just give me one arrays,
with all the values into one array.
你现在问的这个问题有什么问题吗
Any questions on this one you would
ask in an interview right now?
嗯。 > 因此
Yes.
&gt;&gt; So
我们不知道示例阵列的结构是什么吗 ?
we don't know what the structure
of example array is necessarily?
我的意思是，它是一个例子，但它能增加更多的水平还是更少的水平 ?
I mean, it is an example, but
can it add more levels or less levels?
>> 是。
&gt;&gt; Yes.
>> 好。 >> 它可能没有级别。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; It could have no levels.
>> 好。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
>> 它可能只是一个数字的数组。
&gt;&gt; It could just be an array of numbers.
它可能有 30 个不同的阵列嵌套在彼此之间。
It might have 30 different
arrays nested within each other.
你不知道的
You don't know that.
这是一个问题，就像我说的，我以前多次接受采访，
And this is a question that like I said,
I've gotten in multiple interviews before,
所以你一定会有机会参加这次的
so chances are at some point
you'll probably run into this one.
再给点提示，我就不要给你太多提示了，用递归
And give another hint, I shouldn't give
you so many hints, using recursion for
这个会帮你的
this one will help you out.
这让我们更容易理性
It makes it easier to reason about.
您不必使用递归。
You don't have to use recursion.
你能做到的我什么都不说
You could do it,
I won't say anything else.